♪ [MUSIC] ♪
AZURÍN: This is cocaine.
Cocaine.
LILIANA: 94 50-dollar bills...
KATHERINE: They don't know what's in the suitcases.
Yes or no?
CARLA: I consume, but that amount is not for consumption.
JENNIFER: The reason for your trip to Trujillo?
AZURIN: Let's do the field test.
This contains cocaine.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
WIFE: We didn't know he had that.
KATERINE: They didn't know anything.
[SIRENS]
NARRATOR: Jorge Chávez International Airport,
in Lima, Peru.
Here we work daily to combat drug trafficking,
thanks to the joint work of the different forces of
security, has become the second airport with the highest
drug seizures from Latin America.
Now about 200 people are checking in.
to board the next flight to Amsterdam.
EMPLOYEE: Let me see your passport and boarding pass.
NARRATOR: According to police statistics
Anti-drug, this city is fourth on the list of destinations
hot and is one of the most attractive spots in Europe
for drug trafficking networks.
For this reason, officers are increasing surveillance.
AZURÍN: May I have your passport, please?
CÓRDOVA: We were at one of the airline counters.
bound for the city of Amsterdam,
with the support of the anti-drug canine unit staff
and the dog reacted to some luggage that was there
behind the counters.
[BACKGROUND VOICES]
CORDOVA: Apparently there could have been drugs inside.
of those suitcases.
AZURÍN: Let's go get the passengers...
NARRATOR: The police have identified the owners
of suspicious luggage, but finding them is not so simple:
These are two passengers who have already mingled with the large crowd
airport public.
AZURIN: Sorry, sorry, sorry...
[BUSTLE]
NARRATOR: They finally find them in one of the stores
from the second floor.
NARRATOR: They are two young tourists of Spanish nationality
Ukrainian and starting a dialogue is a complication...
CORDOVA: They were two young men who had checked themselves,
and hurriedly left the check-in area.
They didn't speak Spanish, they understood very little English.
Even so, they were able to understand that it was going to be done.
a routine inspection and lead them to proceed
to have their bags inspected.
AZURÍN: How did you come to the country if you don't even speak English,
You don't speak Spanish...? You don't speak anything!
NARRATOR: Language difficulty is a
of the problems they usually face
airport police.
And although it is nothing more than an awkward situation when it is not
discovers nothing illicit, now the first passenger to submit
the inspection is becoming more and more tense.
...let's see how full it is.
This is cocaine.
NARRATOR: The agents proceed to perform the chemical test.
which will allow them to establish whether the substances they have found
are illegal.
JOSEPH: Positive.
AZURÍN: This is proving that it is cocaine.
cocaine, cocaine, cocaine...
UKRAINIAN: Huh?
You are under arrest.
-OK. OK. -OK. OK. OK.
NARRATOR: The visibly nervous passenger
has immediately admitted the crime.
However, strangely when the turn approaches
to inspect his friend's suitcase,
His nervousness becomes even more noticeable than in his own
revision.
NARRATOR: On the contrary, the second young man shows himself
confident, sure of not carrying anything illegal
in your luggage.
And he calmly awaits the results of the chemical analyses.
of the agents.
For him, the outcome will be simply inexplicable.
AZURÍN: We are checking right now,
which has reacted with a turquoise coloration
which is positive for cocaine alkaloid.
positive for cocaine alkaloid...
NARRATOR: The next international flight of the day
will leave for Panama in a few minutes.
The officers of the Customs Superintendence
They have noticed excessive nervousness in a young couple
and proceed to check your luggage.
FRANCISCO: These passengers were very nervous,
They indicated that they had been here in Peru for 8 days,
who only visited the city of Lima,
and who did not have time to do other types of tourism
internal.
It looked very suspicious, which raised the profile.
of the passengers.
NARRATOR: However, the contents of the suitcases are
normal, the inspection seems finished and the couple
is about to resume its path.
But one of the drug-sniffing dogs
He smells something strange in the very structure of the luggage.
Ah, ah, ah, shh, shh.
[BACKGROUND DIALOGUES]
Customs officers summon the police
anti-drug.
Specialists can observe that the background
of the suitcases is unusual.
KEYLLA: At that time the couple was quite
concerned.
They started hugging each other, as if to say, we've already lost,
and that's where it all ended.
KATHERINE: Yes, he already painted.
Positive for cocaine alkaloid.
You are being detained by the National Police of
Peru, Anti-Drug Department, for attempting to transport drugs
abroad.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NARRATOR: Two Ukrainian friends who intended to fly to
Amsterdam were arrested when it was discovered
who were transporting cocaine hidden in their luggage.
NARRATOR: Strangely, while one of the captured accepted
all charges, the other has reacted with disbelief.
NARRATOR: The young people are taken to the offices
of the Anti-Drug Directorate, to continue with the process
in the presence of the prosecutor assigned to the case.
AZURÍN: On this side.
NARRATOR: Now, the agents' task is to extract all
cocaine camouflaged in different products.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪ [NOISES]
UKRAINIAN: Yes.
CORDOVA: The detainee is indicating that,
that there is cocaine there.
In the content of that talc there is.
Now let's verify it with the field test.
Turquoise blue, positive for cocaine alkaloid.
It's a knife holder.
CORDOVA: There are...
cocaine alkaloid.
cocaine alkaloid...
NARRATOR: The detainee points out which objects are
contaminated.
UKRAINIAN: No.
OFFICER: There aren't any? UKRAINIAN: No, no.
CÓRDOVA: They carved it, it's a carving.
NARRATOR: Just as it happened at the time of his arrest,
The first of the Ukrainian passengers openly collaborates
with the police.
Now the officers are preparing to inspect the luggage.
of the other passenger.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
..yes with the camera...
AZURÍN: Here we have a container, which has a logo,
apparently with a language of...
from there, from Ukraine.
Let's check if, if it's what we think, right?
Let's do the field test.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
This contains cocaine.
NARRATOR: Once again the detainee appears surprised.
As if he had no knowledge of the existence of drugs
among his belongings.
But finally his friend says something that seems to bring him down...
[FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
NARRATOR: And now he seems eager to explain
the situation to the officers.
CORDOVA: He tried to make us understand through signs.
that he was responsible trying to protect
in a way to his partner.
AZURÍN: Do you understand a little bit of Spanish?
NARRATOR: For the agents there is only one way:
quickly get a translator and with his help,
finally reveal what the true story is
of the young Ukrainians who were trying to transport cocaine
towards Europe.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NARRATOR: Jorge Chávez Airport has
with more than 70 businesses located between the check-in area
and the boarding gates.
Here 7 out of 10 passengers stop to shop before
to board your flight.
A couple who were planning to travel to Panama were captured when they
discovered that they were carrying cocaine hidden in their luggage.
KATHERINE: Positive for cocaine alkaloid....
NARRATOR: The passengers, who say they are on a journey
tourist celebrating his wedding anniversary,
They are surprised by the arrest.
NARRATOR: The young people are transferred to the Directorate
Anti-drug.
NARRATOR: And here, in the presence of the prosecutor assigned to the case,
the procedure continues.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Agents discover that the methodology is sophisticated.
NARRATOR: Cocaine does not have its typical appearance.
powdery and whitish, but appears camouflaged
with the luggage materials.
KATHERINE: They were trying to transport a black drug,
which is the result of the combination of the substance
whitish with a black solid substance.
[Bangs]
NARRATOR: The type called black drug
It is a recently devised stealth mechanism
by drug traffickers.
It consists of subjecting cocaine to a chemical process, giving it
the appearance and color of the rubber.
This is how it can be camouflaged in synthetic sheets
which constitute the bottoms of bags and suitcases,
becoming almost imperceptible.
The police decide to start an interrogation to obtain
network information that would be behind the shipment
of narcotics.
But the passengers claim total ignorance.
of what they are accused.
KATHERINE: How do you explain that those suitcases
are they conditioned with cocaine alkaloid?
WIFE: We didn't know he had that.
KATHERINE: They didn't know anything.
HUSBAND: No.
KATHERINE: Where did you buy those suitcases?
WIFE: Over there in [BEEP].
KATHERINE: In Mexico.
WIFE: Mexico.
KATHERINE: OK.
If you bought that suitcase in Mexico,
Why do you have a Peruvian brand?
WIFE: I didn't know.
I don't know why.
KATHERINE: The lady tells us that those suitcases,
I had bought them in Mexico.
But we were able to notice that those suitcases only
They are obtained here in Peru, because they are Peruvian brands.
I'm asking you again, did you bring those suitcases?
WIFE: Yes.
KATHERINE: ¿Segura?
I tell you because we have cameras throughout the airport.
and we are going to visualize the day you arrived,
Whether or not they are the suitcases, we ask them again,
Did they bring them from Mexico?
HUSBAND: Yes.
KATHERINE: Sure?
They don't know what's in the suitcases.
Yes or no?
Absolutely nothing.
I tell you again, we have cameras here.
We will see your movements and see if those suitcases
They also came from Mexico.
WIFE: Yes.
KATHERINE: Yes, they are your suitcases from Mexico.
NARRATOR: Noticing that the luggage had been altered to hide
The drug is locally manufactured, police say.
with a firm indication.
It allows them to conjecture that the passengers were traveling alone
with two suitcases and that someone contacted them in Lima
to deliver two more suitcases with their illegal cargo
already prepared.
You don't have any luggage here...
It doesn't explain the four suitcases...
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NARRATOR: Two Ukrainian passengers were arrested.
when it was discovered that they were carrying camouflaged cocaine
among his belongings.
AZURÍN: This contains cocaine.
NARRATOR: However, one of them seems to want to take credit
all the guilt.
Now a translator arrives summoned by the police
to help them clarify the situation.
CORDOVA: Given that both people were stating
who only spoke the Russian language,
is that the support of an interpreter was requested
so that we could have more fluid communication.
NARRATOR: The agents prepare to begin
the interrogation of the first of the detainees.
AZURÍN: How do you explain that we have found,
it is...
cocaine in your suitcase?
[FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
JENNIFER: Did your friend deliver what you're transporting?
NARRATOR: The young man insists he is innocent.
and the interrogation must continue with his partner.
A few moments ago, by means of signs,
He implied that he is the only one responsible
of cocaine possession.
But now the police will see if in their final statement
maintains the same version or if he retracts.
JENNIFER: What she's carrying inside her suitcase,
is it yours?
JENNIFER: Every day that she's been here in Peru,
have you only been with your friend?
JENNIFER: And who did you visit that day when you left your friend?
AZURÍN: Trujillo.
JENNIFER: The reason for your trip to Trujillo?
JENNIFER: How do you explain that your partner,
Do you also have cocaine in your luggage?
CORDOVA: He said again that he was the one who gave her the drugs.
in his suitcase.
That he had been the one who had given her the drugs
to his partner.
JENNIFER: And why did you decide to put drugs in your...
his friend's suitcase, without him knowing?
AZURÍN: When you talk about being overweight,
How many kilos of drugs are you carrying in total?
AZURÍN: Do you know what a serious crime this is in Peru?
We understand that you are opening up.
You've come to transport drugs, haven't you?
AZURÍN: We recommend that you are in time to
cooperate, say who gave him the drugs so we can minimize the...
the penalty.
AZURÍN: So we are talking about an organization
in Ukraine with a connection in Peru?
NARRATOR: For the officers, the statement of this detainee
is consistent with his attitudes throughout
the procedure: from his detailed knowledge
from the location of the cocaine to the total weight it was carrying
in both suitcases.
FERNANDO: He weighs two kilos, eight hundred and sixty.
and a gram.
Two kilos point one hundred thirty grams of cocaine alkaloid.
NARRATOR: And, although he insists on his friend's innocence,
This does not prevent both young men from having to face trial.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
AZURIN: The first one says it's all his drugs,
He is responsible for everything, but that will be seen.
in the investigations.
We are only going to limit ourselves to what we have
evident, isn't it?
We found drugs in each of our suitcases.
NARRATOR: Justice will determine the degree
of the defendants' liability if proven
the version of the young people, one of them could remain
free and the other will have to assume the guilt
for the total amount of drugs seized.
For attempting to transport 4 kilos 991 grams of cocaine
could receive a sentence of between 8 and 15 years in prison.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Every year, millions of travelers from all over the world arrive
to Jorge Chávez Airport to visit Peru.
According to statistics, more than 57 percent are tourists
Latin Americans.
The anti-drug police arrested a young couple who were carrying
cocaine packed in his luggage.
The detainees tried to disassociate themselves from the crime,
but his excuses were found to be false.
NARRATOR: The next step is to check the rest of the luggage.
to confirm if they were only carrying drugs in the two suitcases
suspicious.
cocaine, cocaine....
NARRATOR: Finally the officers detect
that the four suitcases are contaminated.
KATHERINE: The person who made this sample,
He has practically done it to perfection of the structure
of the luggage.
NARRATOR: Because the drug is dyed black and fused
with the luggage's own rubber, in this case,
The agents proceed to establish a gross weight.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
It is thus determined that the woman was carrying 6 kilos, 435 grams,
and the man, 6 kilos, 370 grams.
The net weight will be determined later by a chemical expert.
According to Peruvian law, those arrested for trafficking
Drug offenders can get their sentence reduced
If they accept their guilt and provide information about the network
criminal who would have hired them.
The couple who have so far resisted collaborating
with the police procedure,
now you have one last chance.
CHIANG: Who contacts you?
WIFE: Who contacts us?
About what?
CHIANG: So they can come here.
You know what you've come for.
Who will support them...
KEYLLA: It's quite sad to see a couple get involved
in this type of things, since at the time of being sentenced,
They are going to serve a fairly heavy sentence.
NARRATOR: Finally the captured young men did not change
his statements.
The investigation will continue to find out how the events occurred,
and if the marriage bond is true or was it attempted
of a facade to go unnoticed.
For attempting to transport more than 6 kilograms of cocaine each
One, they could receive a sentence of between 8 and 15 years
from prison.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Every day, 224 flights land at Jorge Chávez Airport.
A flight from Spain is now arriving.
and everything goes smoothly.
However, one of the passengers is delayed.
by security personnel, since x-rays detect lumps
suspects in your carry-on luggage.
FRANCISCO: Packages could be seen inside the luggage.
of the passenger.
This is where LAP staff requests support from staff
We went to customs to be able to carry out the control
corresponding.
NARRATOR: At the Customs offices the prevention team
of smuggling and special operations finds a great
amount of hidden low-denomination Euros
inside paper envelopes lined with aluminum.
LILIANA: 94 50-dollar bills...
4 thousand 700...
and, 3 out of 100...
5 thousand.
FRANCISCO: By law, passengers have to declare
If they carry money exceeding 10 thousand dollars,
up to 30 thousand dollars.
After 30 thousand dollars, passengers cannot declare
the money.
It has to be by bank transfer.
NARRATOR: The passenger claims he was unaware
that he had to declare the money.
But by transporting it hidden and distributed in envelopes,
the argument is not credible.
For the officers, this is an undoubted violation,
but it could also be a crime.
STEW: Anyone what they normally do
It is about finding out exactly what the rules are in each country.
and comply with them.
If I avoid complying with the rules,
It is very likely that it is related to some
another illicit act.
NARRATOR: It was established that the total seized is
131, 170 euros.
If you can prove that the money has been acquired from
legal form, the citizen must pay a corresponding fine
30 percent of what was seized.
If the origin of the money cannot be established,
A criminal investigation will be opened for money laundering.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Peru is among the top 10 suppliers
of the planet's food.
In 2015, more than 170 thousand tons were exported by air.
bound for the United States and Europe.
Peru is the world's leading exporter of asparagus,
This product is perishable, and like other foods
fresh produce requires special care.
From the moment the merchandise arrives at the airport until it finally
is loaded onto the plane, it takes between 24 and 96 hours on average.
That is why the terminal has a sector
specially equipped dedicated to storage
and cooling of loads.
Any error in the care of these foods can cause
huge monetary losses and even cause illness
risky.
PAULA: We are going to enter an environment that is between
2 and 4 degrees Celsius.
We take care of storing the perishable cargo that
leaves for export by air, our function is to maintain
the cold chain.
We work 24 hours a day, every day.
With assistance on holidays, Christmas, New Years.
NARRATOR: When the cargo arrives at the terminal it is placed
in the antechamber where the inspection is carried out
safety to ensure that there is no contamination
nor smuggling of illicit substances.
Once it passes the inspection, it is assigned according to its destination
to one of the 6 storage chambers and then
be delivered to the airline.
Inside the warehouse, the temperature at which the
keep the products, it is between 2 and 4 degrees
Celsius, the same as that of a home refrigerator.
If the temperature is lower, some loads are at risk.
from suffering partial frostbite.
On the other hand, if there are more than 5 degrees,
The bacteria will begin to multiply and produce
cross-contamination of food.
That is why the work of the refrigeration sector is vital.
importance when it comes to complying with the protocols in terms of
Safety and hygiene at the International Airport
Jorge Chavez.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
CONTROLLER: Two, zero, four, five, Lima tower,
makes the exit.
NARRATOR: Due to strict security controls,
Before boarding, all passengers pass through the arches
metal detectors as your carry-on luggage passes through one
of the 20 X-ray scanners.
More than 4 and a half tons of prohibited items
are confiscated every month.
EMPLOYEE: This item is dangerous goods.
But scanners are also capable of revealing the presence
of substances that could be narcotics.
This way, sir. I'll help you.
NARRATOR: And now, some suspicious packages were discovered.
among the belongings of a young man who was on his way on a flight
national to the city of Tacna.
That's why the anti-drug police escort him to his offices.
to inspect luggage.
MARILÚ: How old are you?
DETAINED: 23 years old.
MARILÚ: What do you do?
DETAINEE: I am a student and I work.
MARILÚ: Where exactly do you live?
DETAINED: In Tacna.
NARRATOR: For the officers, the passenger faces the search
from your handbag with the peace of mind of someone who is not carrying
nothing illicit.
JOSEPH: We continue.
And.
NARRATOR: Finally the officer finds the packages
suspects.
But the young man maintains his attitude of confidence.
JOSEPH: It has marijuana.
He has marijuana, marijuana...
NARRATOR: When the content is exposed,
The young man surprises the police with his reaction:
readily admits that he is carrying marijuana.
JOSEPH: We found two packages of marijuana.
CARLA: You consume, but that amount is not for consumption.
NARRATOR: Despite the spontaneous confession of the
passenger, the police must comply with the procedure
to confirm by a field chemical test which is
the substance found.
OFFICER: There it is, violet blue.
Positive for marijuana.
Positive for marijuana....
NARRATOR: With the weighing, they determine that it is
of 261 grams of marijuana, 30 times more than the amount
permitted by Peruvian law for personal consumption.
PROSECUTOR: When was the last day you consumed?
DETAINED: Today, in the morning
PROSECUTOR: Do you use marijuana every day?
DETAINEE: Yes.
PROSECUTOR: Do you always travel and bring and carry like this?
DETAINEE: I always travel and take a quantity with me.
I've never taken that amount, because I always...
I used to come here to Lima more often...
CARLA: The young man in his interview states that what he was wearing,
It was for their consumption.
Since he would not return to the city of Lima for two
three months.
NARRATOR: However, while the young man claims not to be
committing any crime, for the police,
It could all be a facade.
PROSECUTOR: We have a young issue here, it is a problem,
because I can actually believe you to a certain extent
that you use drugs, but the law says that a person
may only be transported for consumption up to
8 grams of marijuana.
If it is more than 8 grams, it can be considered that you are
trafficking.
trafficking, trafficking...
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NARRATOR: To ensure the safety of every corner
from Jorge Chávez International Airport,
must be monitored 24 hours a day.
To carry out the task, the staff has a total of
400 strategically distributed security cameras.
Each camera stores its recording for a period of time.
15 days, unless required
for an ongoing investigation.
[ALTO]
Anti-drug police arrested a student who was trying to
traveling to the city of Tacna carrying 261 grams of marijuana
in your hand luggage.
OFFICIAL: Positive for marijuana.
NARRATOR: It is an unusual case at Jorge Chávez Airport,
since this is the only recorded case of this drug
in the last year.
The passenger insists that he is transporting the drugs for commercial purposes.
for personal consumption.
JOSEPH: It's 261 grams.
Of marijuana.
NARRATOR: The young man claims that he was carrying the drugs only
for personal consumption.
However, for exceeding the tolerated amount of 8 grams
By law, he has been arrested on suspicion of trafficking
of narcotics.
MARILU: You're going to make your call.
DETAINEE: Yeah.
MARILU: Yes, but only as a reason to report your situation,
your state, right?
DETAINEE: Of course.
MARILU: The gentleman is being allowed to make his call.
SALDANA: What happened?
NARRATOR: After speaking with his parents,
The young man appears distressed and the police try to
contain it.
PROSECUTOR: Do your parents know you use drugs?
DETAINEE: My parents do know that I use drugs.
Obviously they don't like it but they also know that I'm a,
I mean, they see that I study, I work, I am responsible,
I don't drink, because I don't like to drink alcohol.
PROSECUTOR: You said you used drugs today?
Did you consume yesterday too?
PROSECUTOR: The first thing I'm going to ask is that you have an exam.
toxicological.
To see if what you say is really true.
..what you say is true...
NARRATOR: The passenger will face legal proceedings.
For carrying 261 grams of marijuana you could receive a
sentence of between 8 and 15 years in prison.
But his situation is not yet defined.
He will now be transferred to a hospital where he will undergo surgery.
medical and psychological studies.
If it is proven that you suffer from marijuana dependence,
could be sent to a rehabilitation center.
[SIRENS]
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
During 2016 at Jorge Chavez Airport
A total of 908 kilos of drugs were seized,
of which more than a quarter were seized in 126
findings in the cargo sector.
[Bangs]
OFFICIAL: Positive for drugs.
NARRATOR: All shipments are carefully reviewed
with x-ray equipment, and when something strange is detected,
the canine unit is used, whose sense of smell is not wrong,
to confirm suspicions.
AZURÍN: When we see a very dynamic dog, it will always tend to
to tear the luggage and a more docile dog usually sits
and just tells the guide that he has found something.
NARRATOR: Now a package that was traveling to Finland
is pointed out by one of the 5 anti-drug police dogs.
The signal is clear: when you sit next to the cash register,
The dog is indicating that something illicit is hidden in the shipment.
The agents proceed to review the content
which turn out to be 8 Eskimo-style winter hats.
Apparently it is a shipment that would be in order but suddenly
It is revealed that not everything is what it seems.
CAMERAMAN: They're like hats, right?
JUDITH: Yes. They are hats.
PATRICIA: The reaction is instantaneous.
Turquoise blue, positive for cocaine alkaloid.
Positive for cocaine alkaloid.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NARRATOR: A suspicious package was flagged
by one of the drug-sniffing dogs in the cargo sector
from the airport.
POLICE: Turquoise blue, positive for alkaloid
of cocaine.
NARRATOR: Concealing narcotics in clothing
of dressing is the fourth most seen modality by the agents,
and this experience in numerous similar cases allows them
detect camouflage methods quickly.
[NOISES]
MÉNDEZ: At the base of the Eskimo hat and on the outline
there were two rooms fitted out.
POLICE: You have to take off the cloth so you can spray.
the reagent.
MÉNDEZ: The turquoise blue coloring reaction is
snapshot, it is the positive indicator for alkaloid
of cocaine....
NARRATOR: In the last year, the anti-drug police
has intercepted more than 70 kilograms of camouflaged drugs
with this methodology.
Now the officers must disassemble each garment in order to
count the seized drugs and close
the procedure.
MÉNDEZ: The weight is 1 kilo 408 grams of cocaine alkaloid.
NARRATOR: From now on, justice will continue to investigate.
until we find the gang behind this shipment.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
ROMERO: The national police through the anti-drug division
What he always seeks is to prevent drugs from reaching people by hand.
of consumers and destroy young people,
and other people who are immersed in the consumption of
drugs.
OSCAR: This is the third suitcase we're opening.
We are proceeding with its destruction.
ROMERO: There have been many arrests and seizures
of drugs, especially the drug dealers from Eastern Europe.
SALDAÑA: However, despite the fact that they know that here
security controls are extremely strict,
risk this type of illegal activities.
AZURIN: So we are talking about an organization
in Ukraine with a connection in Peru.
LOAYZA: Seizures increase year after year.
What we do is improve our capabilities
to prevent the largest amount of drugs from leaving
by any means.
JOSEPH: We found two packages of marijuana.
ROMERO: They don't realize the world they're entering.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
They see what is easy and simply lose their minds.
and consciousness as human beings because they are getting involved
in an extremely serious problem.
Regrettable, of course.
LOAYZA: The handling of deception methods is different.
that organizations have to introduce marijuana,
synthetic drugs or cocaine.
However, there have been cases in which attempts have been made
carry marijuana.
POLICE: Positive for marijuana.
LOAYZA: We will be permanently on top of that person.
who commits illegal acts, especially in the area of trafficking
illicit drug use.
BECERRA: The reason for your trip to Trujillo?
ROMERO: We are increasingly trying to strengthen the work
together to improve our seizures
and arrests at the airport.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
[SIRENS] [SPEAKERS]